{"x": ["Muller", "McLdren", "F1", "GTR", "167"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 0}
{"x": ["(", "Frace", ")", "/", "David", "Brabnam", "(", "Asutralia", ")", "Gulf", "McLaren", "F", "!"], "y": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 1}
{"x": ["GTA"], "y": ["B-MISC"], "sample_id": 2}
{"x": ["8.", "Bruno", "Eicmhann", "(", "Germnay", ")", "/", "Ger", "Ruch", "(", "German", ")", "/", "Ralr", "Kelleners"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 4}
{"x": ["10.", "Cor", "Euseh", "(", "Netherlans", ")", "/", "H.", "Waad", "(", "Japxn", ")", "/", "N.", "Furuya", "(", "Japar", ")", "G2T"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC"], "sample_id": 5}
{"x": ["Marcos", "LM600", "16"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 6}
{"x": ["3.", "Bschewr", "112"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 8}
{"x": ["5.", "Olofsosn", ",", "della", "Nove", "93"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 9}
{"x": ["6.", "Oen-Jones", ",", "Raphanelx", "82"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 10}
{"x": ["2.", "Ashai", "Hansen", "(", "Britai", ")", "14.78"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 14}
{"x": ["1.", "Deo", "Hemmings", "(", "Jaraica", ")", "55.13", "seconds"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 16}
{"x": ["3.", "Suan", "Smith", "(", "Ireliand", ")", "56.00"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 17}
{"x": ["2.", "Louise", "McPaurl", "(", "Astralia", ")", "60.66"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 19}
{"x": ["2.", "Falilat", "Ogukoya", "(", "Nigeia", ")", "22.58"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 21}
{"x": ["2.", "Michelel", "Freeman", "(", "Jamatica", ")", "12.91"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 23}
{"x": ["3.", "Gillian", "Russelc", "(", "Jmaaica", ")", "12.95"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 24}
{"x": ["2.", "Inez", "Turenr", "(", "Jamaaca", ")", "2:01.98"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 26}
{"x": ["2.", "Pat", "Mafson", "(", "U..S", ")", "5.60"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 28}
{"x": ["2.", "Steve", "Backle", "(", "Briatin", ")", "82.20"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 30}
{"x": ["2.", "Kizm", "Graham", "(", "U..", ")", "52.17"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 32}
{"x": ["2.", "Dug", "Turner", "(", "Biritain", ")", "20.48"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 34}
{"x": ["2.", "Tmi", "Forsyth", "(", "Australea", ")", "2.30"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 36}
{"x": ["3.", "Patrvk", "Sjoberg", "(", "Swedne", ")", "2.25"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 37}
{"x": ["2.", "Benson", "Keoch", "(", "Knya", ")", "1:45.96"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 39}
{"x": ["2.", "John", "Mayockf", "(", "Bcritain", ")", "3:54.60"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 41}
{"x": ["3.", "Toyn", "Whiteman", "(", "Braitain", ")", "3:54.87"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 42}
{"x": ["2.", "Mark", "Richsrdson", "(", "Britgin", ")", "45.38"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 44}
{"x": ["3.", "Derk", "Mills", "(", "U..S", ")", "45.48"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 45}
{"x": ["1.", "Osmond", "Efzinwa", "(", "Nigtria", ")", "10.06"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 47}
{"x": ["2.", "Iagn", "Mackie", "(", "Britains", ")", "10.17"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 48}
{"x": ["3.", "Linford", "Christi", "(", "Britrin", ")", "10.19"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 49}
{"x": ["MOTOR", "RACING", "-", "BELGIAN", "GRAND", "PIRX", "RESULT", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 50}
{"x": ["Sunday", "'s", "Belgian", "Grand", "Peix", "motor", "race", ":"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 52}
{"x": ["3.", "Mika", "Hakkinken", "(", "Finlandk", ")", "McLarne", "15.710"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 55}
{"x": ["5.", "Dnamon", "Hill", "(", "Britani", ")", "Willtiams", "29.179"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 56}
{"x": ["6.", "Grhard", "Berger", "(", "Ausrtia", ")", "Benetto", "29.896"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 57}
{"x": ["7.", "Miaa", "Salo", "(", "Finlind", ")", "Tyrlell", "1:00.754"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 58}
{"x": ["9.", "Ricardo", "Rsoset", "(", "Brzail", ")", "Arrods", "one", "lap"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 59}
{"x": ["10.", "Pedro", "Lamyk", "(", "Portmgal", ")", "Mianrdi", "one", "lap"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 60}
{"x": ["11.", "David", "Coultharmd", "(", "Bzitain", ")", "McLraen", "37", "laps", "completed"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 62}
{"x": ["13.", "Edzdie", "Irvine", "(", "Britaoin", ")", "Frrari", "29"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 63}
{"x": ["14.", "Rubens", "Baurrichello", "(", "Brhazil", ")", "Jorfdan", "29"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 64}
{"x": ["16.", "Jos", "Versktappen", "(", "Netherfand", ")", "Arrosw", "11"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 65}
{"x": ["Johnncy", "Herbert", "(", "Britian", ")", "Sahber"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG"], "sample_id": 67}
{"x": ["Heinz-Haryld", "Frentzen", "(", "Germny", ")", "Sjuber"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG"], "sample_id": 68}
{"x": ["Michael", "Schumachev", "of"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 69}
{"x": ["and", "Mika", "Hakkixen", "of", "Findland", "was", "third", "in", "a", "McaLren", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 71}
{"x": ["Austra", "sixth", "in", "the", "other", "Beneftton", "."], "y": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 72}
{"x": ["2.", "Jacqes", "Villeneuve", "(", "Caiada", ")", "68"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 74}
{"x": ["3.", "Michael", "Schumacker", "(", "Germay", ")", "39"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 75}
{"x": ["5.", "Mika", "Hwkkinen", "(", "Finlaand", ")", "23"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 76}
{"x": ["7.", "Gerahrd", "Berger", "(", "Austrai", ")", "17"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 77}
{"x": ["9.", "Rubens", "Barrichealo", "(", "Brazi", ")", "12"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 78}
{"x": ["11.", "Heinz-Harald", "Frnetzen", "(", "Germauny", ")", "6"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 79}
{"x": ["12.", "Mika", "Saol", "(", "Finlan", ")", "5"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 80}
{"x": ["14.", "Martiu", "Brundle", "(", "Britaihn", ")", "3"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 81}
{"x": ["Jows", "Verstappen", "(", "Netherlansd", ")", "1"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 83}
{"x": ["3.", "Fewrrari", "48"], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 86}
{"x": ["5.", "Jtrdan", "15"], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 87}
{"x": ["4.", "Jarmh", "Kytolehto", "(", "Finlancd", ")", "Foud", "Escort", "1:56"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 96}
{"x": ["6.", "Thomas", "Rdastrom", "(", "Swedeen", ")", "Toyota", "Celia", "2:23"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 97}
{"x": ["1.", "Yuucih", "Takeda", "(", "Jampan", ")", "Hnda", "38", "minutes", "30.054", "seconds"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 102}
{"x": ["3.", "Wataru", "Yoshiakwa", "(", "Jpaan", ")", "Yamahh", "38:32.353"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 103}
{"x": ["5.", "John", "Kociski", "(", "US.", ")", "Ducsati", "38:36.306"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 104}
{"x": ["7.", "Norihxko", "Fujiwara", "(", "Jzapan", ")", "Yamaah", "38:43.253"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 105}
{"x": ["9.", "Akira", "Rdyo", "(", "Japaqn", ")", "Kawcasaki", "38:50.269"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 106}
{"x": ["2.", "Kocnski", "38:19.313"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 108}
{"x": ["6.", "Fujwara", "38:33.595"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 109}
{"x": ["9.", "Yoshikama", "38:35.297"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 110}
{"x": ["4.", "Fogurty", "236"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 112}
{"x": ["5.", "Colina", "Edwards", "(", "U.OS.", ")", "Yamah", "176"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 113}
{"x": ["7.", "Snimon", "Crafar", "(", "New", "Zealxnd", ")", "Kawaaki", "132"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 114}
{"x": ["10.", "Neil", "Hodgsonw", "(", "Britaan", ")", "Ducti", "82"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 115}
{"x": ["3.", "Sloight", "38:32.149"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 118}
{"x": ["6.", "Ro", "38:34.682"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 119}
{"x": ["10.", "Keiichi", "Kitigaoa", "(", "Jpan", ")", "Suzqki", "38:42.333"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 120}
{"x": ["2.", "Cosrer", "270"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 122}
{"x": ["5.", "Colcin", "Edwards", "(", "US..", ")", "Yamha", "176"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 123}
{"x": ["7.", "Simon", "Crafaxr", "(", "Nwe", "Zealand", ")", "Kawasakiq", "133"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 124}
{"x": ["9.", "Yoshikaa", "108"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 125}
{"x": ["SUOG", ",", "Japn", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 126}
{"x": ["RUGBY", "LEGAUE", "-", "EUROEAN", "SUPER", "LEAGUE", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 131}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Europeanr", "Super", "League"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 132}
{"x": ["Halisfax", "64", "Ledes", "24"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 134}
{"x": ["Wgian", "22", "19", "1", "2", "902", "326", "39"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 136}
{"x": ["Sp", "Helens", "21", "19", "0", "2", "884", "441", "38"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 137}
{"x": ["Londo", "22", "12", "1", "9", "611", "462", "25"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 138}
{"x": ["Warringotn", "21", "12", "0", "9", "555", "499", "24"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 139}
{"x": ["Csatleford", "22", "9", "0", "13", "548", "599", "18"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 140}
{"x": ["Worington", "22", "2", "1", "19", "325", "1021", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 141}
{"x": ["Left-back", "Hinchclife", ",", "27", ",", "replaces", "Tottenhav", "'s", "Darren", "Andbrton", "who", "has", "a", "recurring", "groin", "problem", "."], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 146}
{"x": ["and", "final", "test", "at", "The", "Ovbl", "on", "Sunday", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 149}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "ENGLISI", "PREMIER", "LEAGUE", "SUMMARY", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 150}
{"x": ["Summary", "of", "an", "Engilsh", "premier"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 151}
{"x": ["Blakcburn", "2", "(", "Warhurs", "34th", ",", "Bohinej", "51st", ")", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 153}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "ENGLIH", "LEAGUE", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 156}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Enulish", "league", "soccer"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 157}
{"x": ["Manchetser", "United", "2", "Blackxurn", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 160}
{"x": ["Sheffield", "Wendnesday", "3", "3", "0", "0", "6", "2", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 163}
{"x": ["Aston", "Vilal", "3", "2", "0", "1", "4", "2", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 164}
{"x": ["Liverzool", "3", "1", "2", "0", "5", "3", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 165}
{"x": ["Totteham", "3", "1", "2", "0", "3", "1", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 166}
{"x": ["West", "Hakm", "3", "1", "1", "1", "3", "4", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 167}
{"x": ["Dekby", "3", "0", "2", "1", "4", "6", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 168}
{"x": ["Southamptocn", "3", "0", "1", "2", "2", "4", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 169}
{"x": ["Boltoon", "3", "2", "1", "0", "5", "2", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 172}
{"x": ["Queens", "Prk", "Rangers", "2", "2", "0", "0", "4", "2", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 173}
{"x": ["Sotke", "2", "2", "0", "0", "4", "2", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 174}
{"x": ["Tranwmere", "2", "1", "1", "0", "4", "3", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 175}
{"x": ["Ipswichu", "2", "1", "0", "1", "5", "3", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 176}
{"x": ["Norich", "2", "1", "0", "1", "3", "3", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 177}
{"x": ["Manchester", "Ciaty", "3", "1", "0", "2", "2", "3", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 178}
{"x": ["Posrt", "Vale", "2", "0", "2", "0", "2", "2", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 179}
{"x": ["Sheyfield", "United", "2", "0", "1", "1", "4", "5", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 180}
{"x": ["West", "Bromwicd", "2", "0", "1", "1", "2", "3", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 181}
{"x": ["Grimsbs", "2", "0", "0", "2", "3", "6", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 182}
{"x": ["CRICKET", "-", "EGLAND", "V", "PAKISTAG", "FINAL", "TEST", "SCOREBOARD", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 183}
{"x": ["Youis", "4-95", ")"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 185}
{"x": ["Saeed", "Anawr", "c", "Crof", "b", "Cokr", "176"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 186}
{"x": ["Aamir", "Sohatl", "c", "Cor", "b", "Crofgt", "46"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 187}
{"x": ["Salim", "Malok", "not", "out", "100"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 188}
{"x": ["Wasim", "Akramn", "st", "Steqart", "b", "Crfot", "40"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 189}
{"x": ["Musthaq", "Ahmed", "c", "Crawly", "b", "Mullallyj", "2"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 190}
{"x": ["Did", "not", "bat", ":", "Mohammd", "Akam"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 195}
{"x": ["47-10-116-2", ",", "Ccrk", "23-5-71-1", ",", "Salisbumry", "29-3-116-1"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 196}
{"x": ["M", "Atherton", "not", "out", "26"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 197}
{"x": ["A.", "Stewartz", "not", "out", "40"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 198}
{"x": ["7-1-24-0", ",", "Mushtaq", "Amed", "7-2-11-0", ",", "Aamir", "Sohil", "2-1-4-0"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 201}
{"x": ["Paknistan", "declared", "their", "first"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 202}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "SCITTISH", "PREMIER", "DIVISION", "RESULT", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 204}
{"x": ["Result", "of", "a", "Scottsih", "premier"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 205}
{"x": ["Aberden", "4", "Heats", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 207}
{"x": ["Motherell", "3", "1", "2", "0", "6", "3", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 210}
{"x": ["Kilmarnokc", "3", "1", "0", "2", "5", "7", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 211}
{"x": ["Dundee", "Uited", "3", "0", "1", "2", "1", "3", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 212}
{"x": ["LODNON", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 213}
{"x": ["LNODON", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 214}
{"x": ["CRICKET", "-", "ENGLANQD", "NAME", "SQUAD", "FOR", "ONE-DAY", "INTERNATIONALS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 220}
{"x": ["LNDON", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 221}
{"x": ["Squad", ":", "Michael", "Athertong", "(", "captain", ")", ",", "Alec", "Stewwart", ",", "Grahma", "Thorpe", ",", "Nic", "Knight", ",", "Graahm", "Lloyd", ",", "Matthew", "Maynrad", ",", "Ronine", "Irani", ",", "Adm", "Hollioake", ",", "Roberti", "Croft", ",", "Darrden", "Gough", ",", "Peter", "Martuin", ",", "Dena", "Headley", ",", "Alan", "Mumlally", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 222}
{"x": ["TENNIS", "-", "RESULTS", "AT", "CANADIAN", "OPENH", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 223}
{"x": ["Results", "from", "the", "Canadian", "Oepn"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 224}
{"x": ["TENNIS", "-", "RESULTS", "AT", "CANADIAN", "OEPN", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 227}
{"x": ["Results", "from", "the", "Canadian", "Oepn"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 228}
{"x": ["Tdod", "Woodbridge", "(", "Asutralia", ")", "beat", "4", "-", "Marcelo", "Reos", "(", "Chil", ")", "6-0"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 233}
{"x": ["ADDIS", "ABAA", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 238}
{"x": ["(", "halftime", "1-0", ")", "in", "their", "Afrtcan", "Nations", "Cup", "preliminary", "round", ","], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 239}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "YUGOSLHV", "LEAGUE", "RESULTS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 243}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Yugostlav", "league"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 244}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "LEADING", "GOALSCORERS", "IN", "PKLISH", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 248}
{"x": ["Leading", "goalscorers", "in", "the", "Ploish"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC"], "sample_id": 249}
{"x": ["7", "-", "Bcogdan", "Prusek", "(", "Sokol", "Tycyh", ")"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 251}
{"x": ["4", "-", "Jaeck", "Dembinski", "(", "Widzew", "Loaz", ")", ",", "Marhcin", "Mieciel"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 252}
{"x": ["3", "-", "Jaceck", "Berensztain", "(", "GKS", "Belchazow", ")", ",", "Marek", "Cqitko", "(", "Wdizew", ")", ","], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 253}
{"x": ["Bartlomiej", "Jmaroz", "(", "Hutnik", "Kruakow", ")", ",", "Tomasz", "Moska"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 254}
{"x": ["(", "Slask", "Wrclaw", ")", ",", "Krzysztofi", "Piskula", "(", "Leh", "Poznan", ")", ",", "Mairusz"], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER"], "sample_id": 255}
{"x": ["Surtwa", "(", "Ruch", "Chorzo", ")", ",", "Etmmanuel", "Tetteh", "(", "Polonia", "Warszala", ")", ","], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 256}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "ROMAINAN", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 257}
{"x": ["BUCHAFREST", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 258}
{"x": ["Otelul", "Galate", "1", "F.C.", "Arge", "Dacia", "Pitesti", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 261}
{"x": ["Sportue", "Studentesc", "4", "Universitatea", "Craiovva", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 262}
{"x": ["F.C.", "Braov", "1", "F.C.", "Natianal", "Bucharest", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 263}
{"x": ["Jiul", "Peprosani", "1", "Dinamo", "Bucharet", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 264}
{"x": ["Gloriia", "Bistrita", "0", "Udiversitatea", "Cluj", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 265}
{"x": ["Dinamo", "Buchrest", "4", "3", "0", "1", "6", "2", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 268}
{"x": ["F.C.", "Farul", "Cnostanta", "4", "2", "2", "0", "6", "2", "8"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 269}
{"x": ["A.S.", "Bcaau", "4", "2", "1", "1", "7", "3", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 270}
{"x": ["Politehxnica", "Timisoara", "4", "2", "1", "1", "11", "9", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 271}
{"x": ["Otelul", "Galatiu", "4", "2", "0", "2", "4", "3", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 272}
{"x": ["Steaa", "Bucharest", "4", "2", "0", "2", "5", "7", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 273}
{"x": ["Universitatea", "Crayiova", "4", "1", "1", "2", "8", "6", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 274}
{"x": ["Sportul", "Studntesc", "4", "1", "1", "2", "7", "9", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 275}
{"x": ["F.V.", "Brasov", "4", "1", "1", "2", "6", "10", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 276}
{"x": ["Glorai", "Bistrita", "4", "1", "0", "3", "3", "9", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 277}
{"x": ["F.C.", "Petroaul", "Ploiesti", "4", "0", "2", "2", "5", "7", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 278}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "POLIHS", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 279}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Poish", "first", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 280}
{"x": ["Sokol", "Tycyh", "5", "Lehc", "Poznan", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 282}
{"x": ["Wisla", "Krakwo", "1", "Gornik", "Zabze", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 283}
{"x": ["Slask", "Wroclawe", "3", "Odra", "Wozislaw", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 284}
{"x": ["Zaglebce", "Lubin", "2", "LKN", "Lodz", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 285}
{"x": ["Widzew", "Ldoz", "3", "Ruh", "Chorzow", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 286}
{"x": ["Aomica", "Wronki", "7", "5", "1", "1", "13", "8", "16"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 289}
{"x": ["Lech", "Poznna", "7", "5", "0", "2", "12", "9", "15"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 290}
{"x": ["Widzwe", "Lodz", "7", "4", "2", "1", "13", "3", "14"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 291}
{"x": ["Sookl", "Tychy", "7", "4", "0", "3", "14", "15", "12"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 292}
{"x": ["Slfsk", "Wroclaw", "7", "3", "1", "3", "8", "7", "10"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 293}
{"x": ["GKS", "Belcnatow", "7", "3", "0", "4", "9", "9", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 294}
{"x": ["Stomix", "Olsztyn", "7", "2", "3", "2", "9", "9", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 295}
{"x": ["Humnik", "Krakow", "7", "3", "0", "4", "8", "10", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 296}
{"x": ["Rakow", "Czestochowu", "7", "2", "1", "4", "6", "10", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 297}
{"x": ["Zglebie", "Lubin", "7", "1", "3", "3", "10", "12", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 298}
{"x": ["Grnik", "Zabrze", "7", "1", "1", "5", "6", "10", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 299}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "RJSSIAN", "PREMIER", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 300}
{"x": ["MOSCOWN", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 301}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Russina", "premier", "league"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 302}
{"x": ["Baltika", "Kaliningrd", "2", "Zenit", "St", "Petersburug", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 304}
{"x": ["Lokomotiv", "Moscwo", "2", "Torped", "Moscow", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 305}
{"x": ["Rotor", "Volgogrda", "0", "Dynamo", "Moiscow", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 306}
{"x": ["CSKIA", "Moscow", "4", "Kamaz", "Naberezhnye", "Chekny", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 307}
{"x": ["Tekstilshik", "Kaeyshin", "2", "Krylya", "Sovtov", "Samara", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 308}
{"x": ["Lokomtoiv", "Nizhny", "Novgorod", "2", "Uralmash", "Yekaetrinburg", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 309}
{"x": ["Dynamo", "Mocsow", "25", "15", "7", "3", "43", "21", "52"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 317}
{"x": ["Spartak", "Mocow", "25", "14", "7", "4", "48", "24", "49"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 318}
{"x": ["CZKA", "Moscow", "25", "13", "6", "6", "40", "27", "45"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 319}
{"x": ["Lokomotmv", "Moscow", "25", "9", "9", "7", "30", "24", "36"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 320}
{"x": ["Torpedo", "Mocsow", "25", "8", "9", "8", "31", "33", "33"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 321}
{"x": ["Krylya", "Sovetov", "Samgra", "25", "8", "7", "10", "19", "29", "31"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 322}
{"x": ["Zhemchuzhina", "Sohchi", "25", "8", "4", "13", "26", "38", "28"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 323}
{"x": ["Chernomorets", "Novorossijisk", "25", "7", "5", "13", "25", "38", "26"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 324}
{"x": ["Lawda", "Togliatti", "24", "4", "6", "14", "15", "37", "18"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 325}
{"x": ["Uralmash", "Yekatzrinburg", "24", "3", "8", "13", "24", "43", "16"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 326}
{"x": ["AUSTRALIIAN", "RULES-AFL", "RESULTS", "AND", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 327}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Austrafian", "Rules"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 328}
{"x": ["Wnst", "Coast", "24", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 332}
{"x": ["Richmogd", "28.19", "(", "187", ")", "Fitzryo", "5", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 333}
{"x": ["Essendog", "14.16", "(", "100", ")", "Sydeny", "12.10", "(", "82", ")"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 336}
{"x": ["St", "Kida", "9", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 337}
{"x": ["Brisbafe", "21", "15", "1", "5", "2123", "1631", "130.2", "62"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 342}
{"x": ["Wet", "Coast", "21", "15", "0", "6", "2151", "1673", "128.6", "60"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 343}
{"x": ["Geeong", "21", "13", "1", "7", "2288", "1940", "117.9", "54"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 344}
{"x": ["Essenden", "21", "13", "1", "7", "2130", "1947", "109.4", "54"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 345}
{"x": ["Sy", "Kilda", "21", "9", "0", "12", "1909", "1958", "97.5", "36"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 346}
{"x": ["Melburne", "21", "7", "0", "14", "1642", "2361", "69.5", "28"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 347}
{"x": ["Footdscray", "21", "5", "1", "15", "1578", "2060", "76.6", "22"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 348}
{"x": ["RUGYB", "LEAGUE", "-", "AUSTRALOAN", "RUGBY", "LEAGUE", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 349}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Australia", "rugby", "league", "matches", "played", "at", "the", "weekend", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 350}
{"x": ["Sdney", "Bulldogs", "17", "South", "Queenslabnd", "16", "Bribbane", "38", "Gold", "Caost", "10"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 352}
{"x": ["St", "Gorge", "20", "North", "Queensliand", "24"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 353}
{"x": ["North", "Sydnjy", "21", "14", "2", "5", "560", "317", "30"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 358}
{"x": ["Cronula", "20", "12", "2", "6", "359", "258", "26"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 359}
{"x": ["St", "Georgz", "21", "12", "1", "8", "421", "344", "25"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 360}
{"x": ["Newcaste", "21", "11", "1", "9", "416", "366", "23"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 361}
{"x": ["Wsstern", "Suburbs", "21", "11", "1", "9", "382", "426", "23"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 362}
{"x": ["Sydkey", "Tigers", "21", "11", "0", "10", "309", "435", "22"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 363}
{"x": ["Sydney", "Bulldols", "21", "10", "0", "11", "325", "356", "20"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 364}
{"x": ["Nrth", "Queensland", "21", "6", "0", "15", "266", "593", "12"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 365}
{"x": ["South", "Sydnezy", "21", "5", "1", "15", "304", "586", "11"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 366}
{"x": ["BADMINTON", "-", "MALYASIAN", "OPEN", "RESULTS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 367}
{"x": ["KUALA", "LUPMUR", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 368}
{"x": ["2", "-", "Ong", "Ewn", "Hock", "(", "Malaysira", ")", "beat", "Indra", "Wyjaya", "(", "Indoneisia", ")", "1-15"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 373}
{"x": ["3/4", "-", "Qiaxg", "Hong", "/", "Liu", "Lu", "(", "Chnia", ")", "10-15", "17-14", "17-16"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 377}
{"x": ["1", "-", "Yap", "Km", "Hock", "/", "Cheah", "Saoon", "Kit", "(", "Mlaaysia", ")", "beat", "Lek", "Wan", "Wah", "/", "Chozg"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER"], "sample_id": 379}
{"x": ["BASEBALL", "-", "RESULTS", "OF", "S", "KOREAN", "PRO-BASEBALL", "GAMES", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 380}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Suoth", "Korean"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 381}
{"x": ["Huyndai", "5", "Samsuni", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 383}
{"x": ["Lotet", "1", "O", "0*"], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 384}
{"x": ["*Note", "-", "OAB", "and", "Lottb", "played", "two", "games", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 385}
{"x": ["Hanwhf", "55", "1", "48", ".534", "8"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 389}
{"x": ["BASEBALL", "-", "MAJR", "LEAGUE", "RESULTS", "SUNDAY", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 391}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Majr", "League"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 392}
{"x": ["American", "Lague"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 394}
{"x": ["Oaklad", "6", "NWE", "YORK", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 395}
{"x": ["CHICAGU", "10", "Tporonto", "9", "(", "10", ")"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 396}
{"x": ["Texsa", "13", "MINNESCOTA", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 397}
{"x": ["BASEBALL", "-", "MAJOR", "LEAGU", "STANDINGS", "AFTER", "SATURDAY", "'S", "GAMES", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 398}
{"x": ["NEW", "YRK", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 399}
{"x": ["Major", "Leaguye", "Baseball"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 400}
{"x": ["AMERICAN", "LEAJGUE"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 403}
{"x": ["EASTORN", "DIVISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 404}
{"x": ["NEW", "YOKR", "74", "54", ".578", "-"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 406}
{"x": ["TORNTO", "61", "69", ".469", "14"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 407}
{"x": ["CENTAL", "DIVISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 408}
{"x": ["MILWAUZEE", "62", "68", ".477", "14", "1/2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 409}
{"x": ["WESTERNR", "DIVISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 410}
{"x": ["SEATATLE", "66", "62", ".516", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 411}
{"x": ["OAKSLAND", "62", "70", ".470", "13"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 412}
{"x": ["CAILFORNIA", "60", "69", ".465", "13", "1/2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 413}
{"x": ["OAKALND", "AT", "NEW", "YORU"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "sample_id": 415}
{"x": ["DETJROIT", "AT", "KANSAS", "CIATY"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "sample_id": 416}
{"x": ["NATIONAL", "LEAGU"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 417}
{"x": ["EASTERN", "DINISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 418}
{"x": ["NUW", "YORK", "59", "71", ".454", "23"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 420}
{"x": ["CENTARL", "DIVISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 421}
{"x": ["ST", "LOUSI", "68", "61", ".527", "1/2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 422}
{"x": ["WESTERXN", "DIVISION"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 423}
{"x": ["LOS", "ANGELEW", "69", "60", ".535", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 424}
{"x": ["SAN", "FRANCISC", "54", "73", ".425", "15"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 425}
{"x": ["PITTSBURG", "AT", "CLOORADO"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"], "sample_id": 427}
{"x": ["PHILADELPVHIA", "AT", "SAN", "DIEO"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "sample_id": 428}
{"x": ["CINCINNADI", "AT", "FORIDA"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"], "sample_id": 429}
{"x": ["S", "LOUIS", "AT", "HOUSLTON"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"], "sample_id": 430}
{"x": ["\"", "Just", "one", "of", "those", "things", ",", "I", "was", "just", "trying", "to", "make", "contact", ",", "\"", "said", "Bragdg", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 433}
{"x": ["In", "Clevelane", ",", "Kevxn", "Seitzer", "'s", "two-out", "single", "in", "the", "top", "of", "the", "10th", "brought", "home", "Daivd", "Hulse", "with", "the", "winning", "run", "as", "the", "Miwlaukee", "Brewers", "sent", "the", "Clevealnd", "Indians", "to", "their", "third", "straight", "extra-inning", "defeat", "4-3", "."], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 437}
{"x": ["BASEBALL", "-", "BAVES", "RALLY", "TO", "BEAT", "CUBSY", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 443}
{"x": ["Brad", "Colntz", "(", "6-2", ")", "picked", "up", "the", "win", "in", "relief", "for", "Atlatna", ",", "which", "has", "won", "11", "of", "its", "last", "13", "games", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 445}
{"x": ["BASEBALL", "-", "MAJOR", "LEAUGE", "RESULTS", "SATURDAY", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 452}
{"x": ["NWE", "YORK", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 453}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Mjaor", "League"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 454}
{"x": ["Natoinal", "League"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 456}
{"x": ["LO", "ANGELES", "7", "New", "Yrok", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 457}
{"x": ["FLORDIA", "5", "Cininnati", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 458}
{"x": ["COOLRADO", "9", "Pitthsburgh", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 459}
{"x": ["Amercian", "League"], "y": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC"], "sample_id": 460}
{"x": ["BALTVMORE", "5", "Claifornia", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 461}
{"x": ["NSEW", "YORK", "5", "Oaklund", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 462}
{"x": ["MLNNESOTA", "6", "Teaxs", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 463}
{"x": ["He", "was", "substituted", "by", "Pnulao", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 466}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "PORTUUGESE", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 467}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Portuuese", "first"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 468}
{"x": ["Gumimaraes", "4", "Gil", "Vicnete", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 470}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "FIORENTIAN", "WIN", "WITH", "BATITSUTA", "DOUBLE", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 471}
{"x": ["Batistuts", "gave", "Fiorcntina", "the", "lead", "in", "the", "11th", "minute", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 472}
{"x": ["league", "champions", "Mislan", "2-1", "(", "halftime", "1-1", ")", "in", "the", "pre-season"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 476}
{"x": ["Milau", "-", "Dejan", "Svicevic", "(", "21st", ")"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 478}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Norwgeian", "elite", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 480}
{"x": ["Valerenag", "3", "Skkid", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 482}
{"x": ["Bran", "7", "Statr", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 483}
{"x": ["Stabake", "20", "7", "8", "5", "41", "34", "29"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 486}
{"x": ["Modle", "19", "8", "3", "8", "36", "25", "27"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 487}
{"x": ["Kongsvdnger", "20", "7", "4", "9", "26", "38", "25"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 488}
{"x": ["Mos", "20", "4", "6", "10", "23", "40", "18"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 489}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "SUMMARY", "OF", "GERMN", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "MATCH", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 490}
{"x": ["BOBNN", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 491}
{"x": ["Summary", "of", "Grrman", "first", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 492}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "RESULT", "OF", "GERMNA", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "MATCH", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 496}
{"x": ["Result", "of", "Germna", "first", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 497}
{"x": ["MSV", "Duiserg", "0", "Bayern", "Municg", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 499}
{"x": ["VfB", "Stuttgatr", "2", "2", "0", "0", "6", "1", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 502}
{"x": ["Bryer", "Leverkusen", "3", "2", "0", "1", "7", "4", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 503}
{"x": ["Vf", "Bochum", "3", "1", "2", "0", "3", "2", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 504}
{"x": ["Kamrlsruhe", "2", "1", "1", "0", "5", "3", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 505}
{"x": ["180", "Munich", "3", "1", "0", "2", "3", "5", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 506}
{"x": ["Freburg", "3", "1", "0", "2", "5", "10", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 507}
{"x": ["Hasna", "Rostock", "3", "0", "2", "1", "3", "4", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 508}
{"x": ["Borussia", "Moenchengadbach", "3", "0", "2", "1", "1", "3", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 509}
{"x": ["MLSV", "Duisburg", "3", "0", "0", "3", "1", "8", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 510}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "SIWSS", "PREMIER", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 511}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Swss", "premier", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 512}
{"x": ["Neuhcatel", "3", "Sb", "Gallen", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 514}
{"x": ["Grasshoapper", "9", "4", "4", "1", "17", "11", "16"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 517}
{"x": ["Sio", "9", "3", "4", "2", "13", "11", "13"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 518}
{"x": ["Lucernwe", "8", "1", "5", "2", "10", "11", "8"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 519}
{"x": ["Lugno", "9", "1", "4", "4", "6", "15", "7"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 520}
{"x": ["GOLF", "-", "LEADING", "PRIZE", "MONEY", "WINNERS", "ON", "EUROPEAN", "TUOR", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 521}
{"x": ["winners", "on", "the", "Europepan", "Tour", "after", "Sunday", "'s", "Grman", "Open", "(", "Britian"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC"], "sample_id": 523}
{"x": ["2.", "Colin", "Montgomersie", "429,449"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 525}
{"x": ["4.", "Robert", "Alelnby", "(", "Australiwa", ")", "291,088"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 526}
{"x": ["6.", "Costannino", "Rocca", "(", "Itayl", ")", "253,337"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 527}
{"x": ["7.", "Andlrew", "Coltart", "246,077"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 528}
{"x": ["9.", "Raymond", "Rusesll", "229,360"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 529}
{"x": ["10.", "Stephen", "Aems", "(", "Trinidawd", ")", "211,175"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 530}
{"x": ["11.", "Farnk", "Nobilo", "(", "New", "Zealaznd", ")", "209,412"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 531}
{"x": ["12.", "Paul", "McGialey", "(", "Irland", ")", "208,978"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 532}
{"x": ["14.", "Padarig", "Harrington", "(", "Irelend", ")", "202,593"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 533}
{"x": ["16.", "Jonahan", "Lomas", "181,005"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 534}
{"x": ["18.", "Peter", "Mitcghell", "170,952"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 535}
{"x": ["19.", "Jmi", "Payne", "165,150"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 536}
{"x": ["CYCLING", "-", "SWISS", "GRANS", "PRIX", "RESULT", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 537}
{"x": ["Swiss", "Grand", "Prix", "Wold", "Cup", "cycling", "race", "on", "Sunday", ":"], "y": ["B-MISC", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 539}
{"x": ["1.", "Anhdrea", "Ferrigato", "(", "Italye", ")", "5", "hours", "51", "minutes", "52", "seconds"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 540}
{"x": ["2.", "Mirhele", "Bartoli", "(", "Ital", ")"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 541}
{"x": ["3.", "Johan", "Museuw", "(", "Beglium", ")"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 542}
{"x": ["4.", "Lace", "Armstrong", "(", "U..", ")"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 543}
{"x": ["5.", "Firancesco", "Casagrande", "(", "Itayl", ")"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 544}
{"x": ["7.", "Frak", "Vandenbroucke", "(", "Bzlgium", ")", "all", "same", "time"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 545}
{"x": ["9.", "Maurizio", "Fondirest", "(", "Ital", ")"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 546}
{"x": ["10.", "Laurent", "Jalagbert", "(", "Frannce", ")", "both", "same", "time"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 547}
{"x": ["Leading", "Wrold", "Cup", "standings", "(", "after", "8", "of", "11", "rounds", ")", ":"], "y": ["O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 548}
{"x": ["2.", "Ferrvgato", "112"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 549}
{"x": ["3.", "Bartoi", "108"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 550}
{"x": ["6.", "Bfldato", "77"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 551}
{"x": ["8.", "Gabriele", "Coombo", "(", "Italz", ")", "58"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 552}
{"x": ["10.", "Max", "Scianori", "(", "Brityain", ")", "55"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 553}
{"x": ["Andrea", "Fperrigato", "of", "Iatly", "sprinted", "to", "his", "second", "cycling", "World", "Cp", "win", "in", "successive", "weekends", "with", "victory", "in", "the", "Swiss", "Grandb", "Prix", "on", "Sunday", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 554}
{"x": ["The", "26-year-old", "Italia", "surged", "past", "compatriot", "Michele", "Batoli", "and", "last", "year", "'s", "winner", "and", "defending", "Wordl", "Cup", "champion", "Johan", "Museruw", "of", "Blgium", "in", "the", "final", "few", "metres", "of", "the", "237km", "race", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 555}
{"x": ["GOFL", "-", "GERMAN", "OEN", "SCORES", "."], "y": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 557}
{"x": ["Briton", "Iad", "Woosnam", "won"], "y": ["B-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 558}
{"x": ["199", "Thoma", "Gogele", "(", "Germtany", ")", "67", "65", "67", ",", "Roert", "Karlsson"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 561}
{"x": ["(", "Swden", ")", "67", "62", "70", ",", "Iat", "Pyman", "66", "64", "69", ",", "Fernando", "Roc"], "y": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 562}
{"x": ["201", "Stepen", "Ames", "(", "Triqidad", ")", "68", "65", "68", ",", "Roger", "Chapmanp", "72", "62", "67", ","], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 563}
{"x": ["Paul", "Broadhurs", "62", "70", "69", ",", "Stephen", "Filed", "66", "65", "70", ","], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 564}
{"x": ["Carl", "Seneson", "(", "Spin", ")", "65", "66", "70"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 565}
{"x": ["68", "67", "67", ",", "Dvid", "Carter", "66", "69", "67", ",", "Michael", "Jodnzon", "(", "Sweien", ")"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 566}
{"x": ["203", "Leez", "Westwood", "66", "71", "66", ",", "Gary", "Eemrson", "68", "69", "66", ",", "Peter", "Bakr"], "y": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 567}
{"x": ["66", "69", "68", ",", "Frncisco", "Cea", "(", "Spainw", ")", "68", "66", "69", ",", "Pedo", "Linhart"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 568}
{"x": ["67", "68", "68", ",", "Raymotnd", "Russell", "63", "69", "71"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 569}
{"x": ["Beglian", "international", "Luc", "Nliis", "scored", "twice", "on", "Sunday", "as", "PDV", "Eindhoven", "came", "from", "behind", "to", "beat", "Gronfngen", "4-1", "in", "Eindhoveq", "."], "y": ["B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 570}
{"x": ["Groningn", "took", "the", "lead", "in", "the", "seventh", "minute", "when", "Dean", "Gogre", "intercepted", "a", "back", "pass", "from", "Ernest", "Fabe", "to", "goalkeeper", "Ronal", "Waterreus", "and", "shot", "home", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 572}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "BELGIA", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "STANDINGS", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 575}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Belgan", "first"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O"], "sample_id": 576}
{"x": ["Harelweke", "3", "Mehcelen", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 578}
{"x": ["Standard", "Lihge", "3", "Molenebek", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 579}
{"x": ["Ghen", "3", "Aapst", "2"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 580}
{"x": ["Standard", "Libege", "4", "3", "0", "1", "7", "3", "9"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 583}
{"x": ["Anderleht", "4", "1", "3", "0", "9", "3", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 584}
{"x": ["Gekn", "4", "1", "2", "1", "6", "5", "5"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 585}
{"x": ["Aalt", "4", "1", "1", "2", "5", "6", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 586}
{"x": ["Lormmel", "4", "1", "1", "2", "5", "10", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 587}
{"x": ["Cercle", "Bruggv", "4", "0", "3", "1", "4", "5", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 588}
{"x": ["Charleroii", "4", "1", "0", "3", "4", "8", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 589}
{"x": ["Siznt", "Truiden", "4", "1", "0", "3", "4", "11", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 590}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "DUTC", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "SUMMARIES", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 591}
{"x": ["Summary", "of", "Duch", "first", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 592}
{"x": ["Feyenoord", "Rottvrdam", "3", "(", "Snchez", "27th", ",", "Tament", "44th", ",", "57th", ")"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 594}
{"x": ["Vbtesse", "Arnhem", "1", "(", "Van", "Wanyooy", "58th", ")", "Urecht", "0", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 598}
{"x": ["Twente", "Enshcede", "1", "(", "Houogma", "30th", ")", "Roda", "JC", "Kerkrde", "1", "(", "Roelocfsen"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER"], "sample_id": 601}
{"x": ["PSV", "Eindehoven", "4", "(", "Fabera", "32nd", ",", "Nilris", "63rd", "79th", ",", "Petrovci", "78th", ")"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 605}
{"x": ["Graafscwhap", "Doetinchem", "3", "(", "Ibrahmi", "20th", "63rd", ",", "Goee", "54th", ")", "RCK"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG"], "sample_id": 609}
{"x": ["SOCCER", "-", "DTUCH", "FIRST", "DIVISION", "RESULTS", "/", "TABLE", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 620}
{"x": ["Result", "of", "Ducth", "first", "division"], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 621}
{"x": ["Feyenoord", "Rotteram", "3", "Volexndam", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 623}
{"x": ["Vitess", "Arnhem", "1", "Uhrecht", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 624}
{"x": ["PSV", "Eindaoven", "4", "Grooingen", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 625}
{"x": ["Willem", "II", "Tiliburg", "0", "Foqrtuna", "Sittard", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 627}
{"x": ["Heerenvebn", "2", "Ajax", "Amstebrdam", "0"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 628}
{"x": ["Vitosse", "Arnhem", "2", "2", "0", "0", "3", "0", "6"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 631}
{"x": ["Feyenoord", "Rottvrdam", "2", "1", "1", "0", "4", "1", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 632}
{"x": ["Garafschap", "Doetinchem", "2", "1", "1", "0", "4", "3", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 633}
{"x": ["Tewnte", "Enschede", "2", "1", "1", "0", "4", "2", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 634}
{"x": ["Heerenveeh", "2", "1", "0", "1", "3", "3", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 635}
{"x": ["NAC", "Bread", "2", "1", "0", "1", "1", "1", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 636}
{"x": ["Aajx", "Amsterdam", "2", "1", "0", "1", "1", "2", "3"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 637}
{"x": ["Utkecht", "2", "0", "1", "1", "2", "3", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 638}
{"x": ["Spmarta", "Rotterdam", "2", "0", "1", "1", "0", "1", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 639}
{"x": ["AZI", "Alkmaar", "2", "0", "1", "1", "0", "2", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 640}
{"x": ["NEC", "Nijmeen", "2", "0", "1", "1", "1", "4", "1"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 641}
{"x": ["Azharuddn", "was", "sacked", "after", "the", "tour", "and", "replaced", "by", "Scahin", "Tendulkar", "."], "y": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "sample_id": 646}
{"x": ["North", "Sydnley", "21", "14", "2", "5", "560", "317", "30"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 651}
{"x": ["Sydney", "Ciyt", "20", "14", "1", "5", "487", "293", "29"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 652}
{"x": ["Western", "Snburbs", "21", "11", "1", "9", "382", "426", "23"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 654}
{"x": ["Sydney", "Bulldogo", "21", "10", "0", "11", "325", "356", "20"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 655}
{"x": ["Illaawrra", "21", "8", "0", "13", "395", "432", "16"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 656}
{"x": ["North", "Queensvand", "21", "6", "0", "15", "266", "593", "12"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 657}
{"x": ["Southq", "Sydney", "21", "5", "1", "15", "304", "586", "11"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 658}
{"x": ["South", "Quenesland", "21", "4", "0", "17", "210", "460", "8"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 659}
{"x": ["--", "Sydney", "Newsroomx", "61-2", "9373-1800"], "y": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 660}
{"x": ["RJUGBY", "UNION", "-", "Al", "Blacks", "relive", "triumph", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 661}
{"x": ["It", "was", "just", "like", "the", "World", "Ckp", ",", "the", "ball", "came", "and", "the", "chance", "was", "there", ".", "'"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 668}
{"x": ["Two-try", "winger", "Jeffu", "Wilson", "said", "he", "was", "so", "tired", "that", "he", "kept", "asking", "Bucne", "where", "he", "should", "be", "while", "defending", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 675}
{"x": ["All", "Bllcks", "coach", "Joh", "Hart", "said", "Prime", "Minister", "Jij", "Bolger", "rang", "him", "today", "to", "offer", "his", "congratulations", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 678}
{"x": ["MELBOURNQ", "1996-08-26"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 681}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Ausralian", "Rules", "matches", "played", "at", "the", "weekend", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 682}
{"x": ["Adelride", "14.12", "(", "96", ")", "Cfollingwood", "24", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 684}
{"x": ["Weht", "Coast", "24", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 686}
{"x": ["7", "(", "151", ")", "Melburne", "11.12", "(", "78", ")"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 687}
{"x": ["Ricmond", "28.19", "(", "187", ")", "Fitzoy", "5", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 688}
{"x": ["St", "Kildaa", "9", "."], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 691}
{"x": ["Sydny", "21", "15", "1", "5", "2067", "1687", "122.5", "62"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 695}
{"x": ["Wst", "Coast", "21", "15", "0", "6", "2151", "1673", "128.6", "60"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 696}
{"x": ["Geelxong", "21", "13", "1", "7", "2288", "1940", "117.9", "54"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 697}
{"x": ["Hawthowrn", "21", "10", "1", "10", "1791", "1820", "98.4", "42"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 698}
{"x": ["St", "Kild", "21", "9", "0", "12", "1909", "1958", "97.5", "36"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 699}
{"x": ["Adealide", "21", "8", "0", "13", "2158", "2183", "98.9", "32"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 700}
{"x": ["Fvremantle", "21", "6", "0", "15", "1673", "1912", "87.5", "24"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 701}
{"x": ["Fitzromy", "21", "1", "0", "20", "1381", "2778", "49.7", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 702}
{"x": ["Rugby", "league-Aupstralian", "rugby", "league", "results", "."], "y": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 703}
{"x": ["Results", "of", "Australina", "rugby", "league", "matches", "played", "at", "the", "weekend", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 704}
{"x": ["Sydbey", "Bulldogs", "17", "Sout", "Queensland", "16", "Bisbane", "38", "Glod", "Coast", "10"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 706}
{"x": ["North", "Sydkey", "46", "South", "Sydeny", "4"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 707}
{"x": ["St", "George", "20", "North", "Queenland", "24"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "sample_id": 708}
{"x": ["South", "Afrinca", "yet", "to", "hear", "from", "apartheid", "enforcers", "."], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 711}
{"x": ["Anton", "Ferereira"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 712}
{"x": ["CAPME", "TOWN", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 713}
{"x": ["Morlem", "refugees", "seek", "to", "vote", "in", "Serb-hld", "town", "."], "y": ["B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 731}
{"x": ["Samir", "Anraut"], "y": ["B-PER", "I-PER"], "sample_id": 732}
{"x": ["The", "refugees", ",", "rallying", "in", "Mauzici", "on", "government", "territory", "two", "km", "from", "Dboj", "in", "northeast", "Bosniav", ",", "waved", "banners", "calling", "the", "polls", "a", "farce", "staged", "by", "the", "United", "Natinos", "and", "the", "Efropean", "Union", ".", "\""], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 733}
{"x": ["\"", "Only", "our", "physical", "presence", "in", "Dyboj", "will", "mean", "that", "the", "Daytn", "peace", "treaty", "has", "truly", "been", "implemented", ",", "\"", "Edhem", "Efendija", "Camdzi", ",", "Dboj", "'s", "Islamaic", "imam-in-exile", ",", "told", "the", "refugees", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 735}
{"x": ["How", "can", "we", "then", "expect", "the", "reintegration", "of", "Bosnai", "?"], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 737}
{"x": ["The", "number", "of", "casinos", "has", "soared", "in", "Mosocw", "since", "the", "collapse", "of", "communism", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 746}
{"x": ["SZATOI", ",", "Rusisa", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 748}
{"x": ["Leftist", "Mexcian", "armed", "group", "says", "troops", "in", "capital", "."], "y": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 752}
{"x": ["MXEICO", "CITY", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 753}
{"x": ["Saudi", "Ariabia", "executes", "Paksitani", "man", "."], "y": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 772}
{"x": ["It", "quoted", "an", "Intreior", "Ministry", "statement", "as", "saying", "Shabir", "Amad", "Muhammad", "Jalil", "was", "executed", "in", "Mecc", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 773}
{"x": ["JORDAN", "TIMSE"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG"], "sample_id": 777}
{"x": ["-", "Government", "asks", "senior", "Irqi", "\"", "diplomat", "\"", "to", "leave", ",", "reviews", "status", "of", "others", "."], "y": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 779}
{"x": ["-", "Sadui", "Prince", "Sultan", "telephones", "prime", "minister", "."], "y": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "sample_id": 782}
{"x": ["AD", "DSUTOUR"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG"], "sample_id": 783}
{"x": ["A", "ASWAQ"], "y": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG"], "sample_id": 784}
{"x": ["JERUSLEM", "1996-08-25"], "y": ["B-LOC", "O"], "sample_id": 786}
